<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>coding on Eureka!</title>
    <link>https://johhnmag0.github.io/tables/coding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in coding on Eureka!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 19:41:03 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://johhnmag0.github.io/tables/coding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The ~~Masochist~~ Amazing World of Compilers</title>
      <link>https://johhnmag0.github.io/post/2022/12/11/the-~~masochist~~-amazing-world-of-compilers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 19:41:03 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johhnmag0.github.io/post/2022/12/11/the-~~masochist~~-amazing-world-of-compilers/</guid>
      <description>Introduction It&amp;rsquo;s All Binaries Automatons Roll Out Compiling Flexing my Bison with a Calculator  1.Introduction When we think of computers, particularly programming languages, one of the first questions that should come to mind is, &amp;ldquo;How does the computer understand that?&amp;ldquo;And that is one of the questions that can be answered by analyzing how a compiler works.
Compilers are basically programs that can translate programming languages into computer language. And that is what we are going to talk about in this article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generating Random Passwords</title>
      <link>https://johhnmag0.github.io/post/2022/09/09/generating-random-passwords/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 13:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johhnmag0.github.io/post/2022/09/09/generating-random-passwords/</guid>
      <description>Generating Random Passwords  Introduction Why Computers can&amp;rsquo;t Generate Random Numbers? /dev/urandom and /dev/random Implementing a CLI on Linux  1.Introduction I have been taking some classes at the university these last few weeks, and we started to get a grasp on the C programming language, and I really like the idea of seeing how things work under the hood. But I really think that the best way to see if you are really getting somewhere is to make some projects, and one of the things that I consider very useful but we don&amp;rsquo;t have that by default on Linux is a random password generator, so I decided to create a simple CLI program that does exactly that generates random passwords.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2fa Authentication PHP</title>
      <link>https://johhnmag0.github.io/post/2022/08/08/2fa-authentication-php/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 21:34:25 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johhnmag0.github.io/post/2022/08/08/2fa-authentication-php/</guid>
      <description>Introduction What is the OTP? URI Format Enconding with Base32 Generating a QRCode  1.Introduction For the last month, I have been working on a library for PHP that will implement the OTP(One Time Password) in an easy way. In the following topics, I will try to explain each technology and protocol that were used to build this software. If you don&amp;rsquo;t want to pass for this technical stuff, you can just go to the explanation of the library.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
